

Phone: 4491096926

Email: angelalvarezflores@gmail.com

Website:

angelalvz.000webhostapp.com

ABOUT ME

I am a Full Stack Web Developer with more than 3 years of experience. I honestly love what I do because through my programming, I can create tools that make people's tasks easier

SKILLS HTML5 & CSS3 PHP NODE JS / REACT JAVA (SWING) C# / .NET GIT KANBAN/SCRUM SQL Server / MySQL

ÁNGEL ÁLVAREZ WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

(June 2019 - December 2020)

WEB DEVELOPER

INEGI

- Developed a system (C#, ASP.NET, ReactJS, Bootstrap) to manage and display information from different processes of the 2020 population and housing census
- Developed a web tool for sending mass mailings with AWS
- Participated in the project "Cénsate tú mismo", applying performance and design improvements

(November 2017 – November 2018)

SOFTWARE ANALYST / WEB DEVELOPER

VITROHOGAR DE AGUASCALIENTES

- Developed a web system (PHP MVC, Bootstrap) for the administration of hierarchically assigned tasks, using a dashboard
- Developed a desktop application with Java Swing to make a comparison of the inventory of all the companies products
- Fixed bugs in the ERP (Intelisis), modifying Stored Procedures in SQL Server.
- Good knowledge of SQL Server for reporting to different departments

(October 2016 – September 2017)

WEB DEVELOPER / PROJECT MANAGER

KIUBIX

- Web systems developer using PHP with Yii2 and Laravel framework
 - REST API's development with Lumen
 - As a coordinator, I managed the entire software development process for two ERP systems with a team of three people under my direction, using agile development methodogies (Scrum, Kanban)

EDUCATION

(August 2011 – December 2015)

I.T. ENGINEERING

INSTITUTO TECNOLÓGICO DE AGUASCALIENTES